all right I just told this story but the
yoga studio is very echoey so I just
wanted to retell it and I don't want to
wait till I get home because then I
might not be in a space too old to tell
it so something significant happened on
my journey and although I'm still
figuring out the significance I wanted
to share it in its current state I have
been wearing and I'm sure you've seen
that I was wearing a necklace for months
the reason that I put it on is a little
bit private but it was because someone
explained to me in for a nation's
tradition that it was done for
protection and so I put it on and that
is significant also for the story that
it was about my project and putting out
about finding people for my project and
I found someone who was known at all
that but was exactly what I needed in
that moment to get my next health leap
forward as well as project so I've been
wearing this for months and today it
broke today isn't just any other day
today is also the birthday of the person
who gave me this necklace and almost
seven years ago about two weeks after
his birthday he died from suicide and me
pregnant with my daughter very pregnant
with my daughter
seven months pregnant with my daughter
caught on a Greyhound bus and went to
Alberta
to say goodbye and that was the last
time I was in Lethbridge where I grew up
I don't have any family left there I
stayed with one of my other good friends
that dated him before she's not married
with kids he at one point moved out here
and we were roommates he moved out to
Vancouver and right after he moved in
with me
I got diagnosed with my brain tumors and
went through surgery
watched him go through his addiction to
pot and then the guilt associated with
not talking to him - birthday him never
getting to meet my daughter it's a lot
there's a lot there and but today
the fact that it broke off today on his
birthday is significant and that's about
how significant my signs are from the
universe a lot of the time when I have
to be paying attention cuz it could have
broken off on any day and also could've
just broken off on his birthday but it
broke off in an area I didn't expect it
to break it also happened well I was
watching a video on a debt Jubilee by
Charles Einstein and Zach Geist and the
reason I can remember those names is
well watching it I remember thinking as
soon as it was that Geist it was like
that's like zeitgeist and Erik
introduced him to the zeitgeist movies
and I introduced him to the zeitgeist
movement and the zeitgeist movement
resource-based economy' it's a big piece
of what I'm trying to create in the
world like how we actually get there I
know how we can actually incremental II
get there and in this game be space that
I've been in for the last month
I keep hearing Jubilee I keep hearing my
name
Remzi mentioned it he's talks about
having the common planet is about the
debt Jubilee but more so he was like we
will include into it the exact moment we
were having a conversation we're like oh
that's what I talked about it bubble
Jubilee and I was talking to Jordan Hall
same thing he was talking about a
project called you bleed Jubilee project
and how that works and now this which I
found from the game be Facebook group
but also this concept is very can be
deadly
my whole life that has been
and now after last weekend's where I got
the piece of like I am part of the story
it's not just like I happened to be the
person who happens to know how we create
this world none of it is about that I'm
better than other people because it's
coming through me I know that it's I
have to become the person who's worthy
of this coming through and no I don't
because it's I don't know I don't even
know what it means but I'm sitting with
it and I wanted to share it because
that's a piece of it sharing this stuff
as it comes up how these things happen
that are significant and after having
told this story previously in the yoga
studio and then coming down here and
selling it in the craft studio he
Herrick intertwines everything he's
intertwined even in my project it
happened long after he was gone but the
fact that he introduced me to sight guys
the fact that I was wearing this
necklace the fact when this all happened
but he's also intertwined with two of
the biggest learnings in my life which
are my brain tumors and what came after
that and my child being born and he
didn't get to meet her but I traveled
with her to see him and there's
something significant there that this
happened
around the end of her life at the end of
his life in the beginning of hers I
don't know all of the significance but I
wanted to share this story because that
is what I'm here to do it share the
story of me creating Mead me creating
the spark that creates the thing that we
create together it is a debt Jubilee
that is it sets all of us free from the
slavery of capitalism and that my name
is Jubilee is starting to it's she
proving itself to be significant to me
but like by it repeating yes repeat
again and again that's had to break off
well I was watching the video does
anyone else have those things happen
please share in the comments if you do
I would love to hear it like does the
universe hit you over the head with
things include lips like I am that it
needs to be like thing upon thing upon
thing for you to get the message I hear
you
thank you